Guide to the Contest responses to Lenore Skenazy's "Only in New York" and "New York Stories" columns, New York Daily News, 1988-1995 MS 3232
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. "New York Stories" contest responses, 1992-1995
  - NYS Contest 148. What war story can you never forget? [results published September 18, 1994] (Offsite-box 9)
  - NYS Contest 149. What's your most vivid memory about TV? [results published September 25, 1994] (Offsite-box 9)
  - NYS Contest 150. What's the wildest conversation you've had with a child? [results published October 2, 1994] (Offsite-box 10)
  - NYS Contest 151. What was the most remarkable thing you found while looking for something else? [results published October 9, 1994] (Offsite-box 10)
  - NYS Contest 152. Who was the most annoying person you were ever stuck sitting next to? [results published October 16, 1994] (Offsite-box 10)
  - NYS Contest 153. What's your weirdest coincidence story? [results published October 23, 1994] (Offsite-box 10)
  - NYS Contest 154. What extremely silly thing did you want more than anything else when you were a kid? And what happened when (and if) you got it? [results published October 30, 1994] {question posed as #153, a typo in paper} (Offsite-box 10)
  - NYS Contest 155. What's the wackiest thing that ever happened to you at a sporting event? [results published November 6, 1994] (Offsite-box 10)
  - NYS Contest 156. When did a stranger brighten your day? [results published November 13, 1994] (Offsite-box 10)
  - NYS Contest 157. When were you even a tiny part of history? [results published November 20, 1994] (Offsite-box 10)
  - NYS Contest 158. What little bit of conversation can you be sure you'll hear at a family gathering? [results published November 27, 1994] (Offsite-box 10)
  - NYS Contest 159. What's the cutest thing your pet ever did to win your attention? [results published December 4, 1994] (Offsite-box 10)
  - NYS Contest 160. What's your happiest memory of a place that exists no more? [results published December 11, 1994] (Offsite-box 10)
  - NYS Contest 161. What strange information did your mother or father give you about the opposite sex? [results published December 18, 1994] (Offsite-box 10)
  - NYS Contest 162. What awkward bit of information did your child choose to disclose? [results published January 8, 1995] (Offsite-box 10)
  - NYS Contest 163. What person, place or thing came unexpectedly back into your life? [results published January 15, 1995] (Offsite-box 10)
  - NYS Contest 164. When did a creep or a saint get what they truly deserved? [results published January 22, 1995] (Offsite-box 11)
  - NYS Contest 165. What real life ghost story happened to someone in your family? [results published January 29, 1995] (Offsite-box 11)
  - NYS Contest 166. Under what circumstances did you ruin something you really liked? [results published February 5, 1995] (Offsite-box 11)
  - NYS Contest 167. How did you once wrap someone around your little finger (or get wrapped around someone else's)? [results published February 12, 1995] (Offsite-box 11)
  - NYS Contest 168. What wacky thing did you (or a friend) attempt as a child, not knowing it was impossible? [results published February 19, 1995] (Offsite-box 11)
  - NYS Contest 169. What annoying thing were you forced to do that turned out to be a blessing? [results published February 26, 1995] (Offsite-box 11)
  - NYS Contest 170. What question(s) would you like to ask your pet, if you could communicate? [results published March 5, 1995] (Offsite-box 11)
  - NYS Contest 171. When did you first realize not all families do everything the same way yours does? [results published March 19, 1995] (Offsite-box 11)
  - NYS Contest 172. What lyrics did you sing wrong for a while? [results published March 26, 1995] (Offsite-box 11)
  - NYS Contest 173. When did you suffer for a good deed you did? [results published April 2, 1995] (Offsite-box 11)
  - NYS Contest 174. What is the strangest encounter you ever had with a household pest? [results published April 9, 1995] (Offsite-box 11)
  - NYS Contest 175. What's the most memorable thing that happened to you or a relative when you first arrived in New York? [results published April 16, 1995] (Offsite-box 11)
  - NYS Contest 176. What object always brings back a specific memory? [results published April 23, 1995] (Offsite-box 11)
  - NYS Contest 177. How did you and your buddies get your nicknames? [results published April 30, 1995] (Offsite-box 11)